[{"answer": "Yeah, but I've seen pictures of her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I think I'd rather go out on a deaf date than a blind date. The question is whether you'd rather date the blind or the deaf", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Wait a minute. I must have been winking down at the office. That's why Mr. my friend was acting so mysteriouso", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hu, oh. No he thought I was hiding something from him about my friend.", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend! Ah, ha, Hello! Phew!", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Grandma Memma", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, I think I would have remembered my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What are you saying? . . . Salad! What was I thinking? Women don't respect salad eaters", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "But you're going over there for dinner tonight, right", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Who told you to sell the card", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No I didn't", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well Stubs has already sold it to some guy who's kid's in the hospital ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Look, do you want me to get it back or not", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well get it back! It's very important.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Get it back!", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I would askk you to stay tonight but I only have the sofa bed and it's where I sleep", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Head to toe", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "We'll have to sleep head to toe", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Head to toe.", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm sorry I didn't get any sleep you kept kicking me in the face", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I'll make them later. Uh. ", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I mean, why? Why would I take her stupid napkins", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "They were", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Because they were in the pockets of my jacket", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes. I was using them to spit out the mutton", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "They were", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Spit it out? I had dogs chasing me for that mutton. I was almost mauled because of that mutton", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You spent the night at my friend's? Did we", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Reversed positions", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "That, that's ridiculous. I'm not a home run hitter", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "He did not", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Hey. What's all this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I thought we were going out", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Oh, by the way, tomorrow night, my friend has to catch a fly ball in his hat", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "And you were probably just going to stick it in an envelope", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Oh, the dogs did that but it wasn't their fault, somebody stuffed some strange meat in the pocket", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wink.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Could have been", "qsentId": 38}]